A Finding Aid to the Francis V. O'Connor Papers, 1920-2009, in the Archives of American Art AAA.oconfran
Archives of American Art
- NCFA Library, 1920-1973; Series 1; 6.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-7, OV 28
  - WPA/FAP Artists' Files, 1936-1971; 1.2
    - Ptylak, Leonard, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Rackley, Mildred, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Ramer, Nathaniel, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Refregier, Anton, 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Reisman, Philip, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Ritter, Chris, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Rollo, Jo, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Romano, Emanuel G., 1937-1968 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Rothschild, Lincoln, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Rugolo, Joseph, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Sanders, Adam A., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Sanger, Isaac J., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Schafranck, Louis, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Schreiber, Georges, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Shokler, Harry, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Sokole, Miron, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Solman, Joseph, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Soyer, Isaac, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Soyer, Moses, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Spivak, Max, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Steffen, Bernard, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Stenbery, Algot, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Surovell, Samuel, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Sussman, Richard N., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Taylor, J.W., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Theodore, Ion, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Tytell, Louis, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Van Veen, Stuyvesant, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Von Wolf, Henry, 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Varian, Dorothy, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Vukovic, Marko, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Wahl, Theodore, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Ward, Lynd K., 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Whiteman, Frederick J., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Witonski, Fred (Ted), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Witonski, Isabelle Greenberger, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Wolins, Joseph, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Yaghjian, Edmund, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - PWAP, Coye, Lee Brown, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Section, Albriszio, Humbert, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Section, Amateis, Edmond, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Section, Biddle, George, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Section, Billings, Henry, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Section, Cecere, Gaetano, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Section, Citron, Minna, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Section, Dinneen, Alice, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Section, Donnelly, Thomas, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Section, Dows, Olin, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Section, Edie, Stuart, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Section, Etnier, Stephen, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Section, Logan, Elizabeth, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Section, Mangravite, Peppino, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Section, Margoulies, Berta, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Section, Picken, George, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Section, Rudy, Charles, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Section, Samstag, Gordon, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Section, Sardeau, Helene, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Section, Taylor, John W., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Section, Wilson, Helen, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - TRAP, Barbarossa, Theodore C., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - TRAP, Barile, Xavier J., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - TRAP, Barthe, Richmond, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - TRAP, Blanche, Arnold, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - TRAP, Cadmus, Paul, 1942-1968 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - TRAP, Dohanos, Stevan, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - TRAP, Donnelly, Thomas, 1938-1968 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - TRAP, Glinsky, Vincent, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - TRAP, Goff, Lloyd L., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - TRAP, Janowsky, Bela, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - TRAP, Kaplan, Joseph, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - TRAP, Knight, Frederick, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - TRAP, Lane, Harry, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - TRAP, Lozowick, Louis, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - TRAP, Picken, George, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - TRAP, Rackley, Mildred, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - TRAP, Reindel, Edna, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - TRAP, Sanstag, Gordon, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - TRAP, Shokler, Harry, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - TRAP, Stenbery, Algot, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - TRAP, Weston, Harold, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - GSA Artists' Employment History Records, 1936-1973; 1.3
    Files are of artists, Index of American Design personnel, teachers, administrators, and supervisors employed by the FAP, TRAP, and Treasury Section divisions. These employment forms were made for O'Connor's FSVA project by the National Personnel Records Center in St. Louis. The records were compiled from microfilmed employment records and represent an effort to create a complete list of New York WPA artists and administrators. Files of individual names contain additional material on artists including original research notes, resumes, correspondence, and printed material. Printouts of employment transcript data are also included.
    - Anonymous, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - A, circa 1967 (Box 4, Folder 104)
      Forms for the following artists: Abernathy, Harry; Abernathy, Inez; Abrahams, Archie; Abrahamson (Abramson), Hershel; Abramovitz, Albert; Acamphora, Nicholas; Acramonte, Humbert; Adams, Bertrand R.; Adams, Charles W.; Adelman, Lillian; Adelman, Paul; Adler, Fred; Adler, Joseph; Afroyim, Beys; Aidone, Mary; Aiken, Elizabeth; Albinio, Nicholas; Alger, John; Allan, Harry; Alland, Alexander; Allen, Anne; Allen, Eleanor C.; Almgren, Jenny E.; Aloisi, Anna; Alshets, Simon; Alston, Charles H.; Alter, Eli; Amantea, Nicholas; Amenya, Yosei; Amero, Emilio; Anchel, Harold; Andrews, Robert; Angell, Blanche; Annunziata, Nicola; Archer, Robert; Artman, Jean; Aucello, Salvatore; Ault, Beatrice; Austin, Helen; Ausubel, Sheva; Autorino, Lucille; Avery, Milton; Azzaretti, Faust
    - Abraham, Arthur, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Adams, Bert, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Allen, John, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Anderson, Carlos, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Ault, George C., 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Ba-Bj, circa 1967 (Box 4, Folder 110)
      Forms for the following artists: Bader, Herman; Badin, Ferdinand; Baker, Grace Green; Baker, Oliver M.; Balvage, Thomas J.; Banaseqicz, Ignatius; Bannarn, Henry; Barber, Herbert C.; Barbieri, Fred; Barbieri, Grace; Barbu, Elena; Bard, Philip; Barish, Anna; Barron, Joseph; Barry, Don; Basky, Frank; Bate, Isabel; Bayard, Lucie; Baylinson, Abraham; Beach, Beata; Bechter, Fred H.; Beck, Morris; Becker, Fred; Beer, Doris R.; Bell, Enid; Belthorne, Vincent; Benge, Jessie M.; Bennern, Henry; Bentley, John W.; Bentz, John; Berge, Virginie; Berler, Monroe; Berlin, Paul; Berlow, Philip; Berner, Mary; Bernstein, Aline; Bernstein, David; Bernstein, Meyer; Bernstein, Morris; Besedick, Frank; Bethune, Norman; Beulah, Grace; Bialostosky, Ruth; Biasetti, Leonida; Bibol, Philip; Biel, Joseph; Bills, Richard; Binney, Ida; Bjorn, Aleth C.
    - Bl-Bz, circa 1967 (Box 4, Folder 111)
      Forms for the following artists: Black, Arnold; Black, Howard;, Blanch, Lucile (Lucille); Blazy, Sterling; Bloch, Julius; Block, Fanny; Bluestein, Selma; Blumenfeld, Maurice; Blumenstiel, Helen; Bondi, Andrew; Bordeaux, Sadie; Borelli, Francis; Borisov, Saul; Borrazzo, Salvatore; Botts, Hugh; Bowen, John; Bowes, Julian; Bowler, Harold; Boyd, Julia; Brady, Warren; Bragg, Diana; Brandfield, Dayton; Brantham, Eric; Braun, Clayton; Braunfield, J.; Braunstein, Ben; Braverman, Barnet; Breckenridge, Alexander W.W.; Breidvik, Mons; Breinin, Raymond; Brennecke, Muriel; Breslow, Louis; Briggs, Judson; Brodeur, C.E.; Brodsky, George; Bromberg, Louis; Brown, E.; Brown, Helen; Browne, Byron; Browne, Ross; Brunder, Thelma; Budash, Frank; Burchess, Arnold; Burling, Dennie; Burlingame, Dennis; Burliuk, David; Burstyn, Jerome; Burzy, Vincent; Busa, Peter; Busenbark, Ernest; Byer, Alexander
    - Baker, Don, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Baziotes, William, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Benn, Ben, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Bennett, Gwendolyn, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Ben-Shmuel, Ahron, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Benson, John W., 1936-1968 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Black, Harold, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Block, Dorothy, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Block, Lucienne, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bolton, Clarence, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Borne, Mortimer, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Bosa, Louis, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Botto, Otto, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bouche, Louis, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bowden, Harry C., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Braverman, Ernest, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Bruback (Trubach?), E., circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Burke, David, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Burke, Selma, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Burlin, Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - C-Ch, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Forms for the following artists: Cabanaugh, John; Coloenesco, Aurelio; Campbell, Blendon; Campbell, Rollington; Campton, James S.; Campton, Louis S.; Candell, Victor; Capaldo, Ernest; Capelli, Giancinto; Carano, Vincent; Carles, Jeanne; Carlomango, William; Carlotte, Ida; Carman, Albert; Carney, Wilfred (William); Carpenter, Margaret; Cartier, Ferdinand; Cary, Lucian; Cassell, Lillian M.; Castaing, Camille; Cavalito, Albina (Cavallito, Albino); Cedarquist, Arthur; Celetano, Daniel; Cerney, George; Chalman, Walter V.; Chaney, Ruth; Charlot, Jean; Chase, Ethel; Chavez, Edward A.; Chernoff, Vadim; Chianese, Ralph; Choate, F.
    - Ci-Cz, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Forms for the following artists: Clark, Mae A.; Cleary, Joseph W.; Clum, Harold; Coffey, Neva (Nova); Cohen, George; Cole, Robert B.; Colgan, Joseph; Collins, Pat; Colman (Coleman), Fred; Concha, Margaret; Conklin, Bella; Contini, Adolph; Cooperman, Abe; Copen, Herman; Corbino, Jon; Cordaro, Aurelio; Corso, Antonio; Costa, Francis; Coussirat, Elizabeth; Coville, Earl; Cramer, Percy W.; Crichlow, Ernest; Crimi, Charles; Crimi, Nancy; Crockwell, Douglass; Cross, Lincoln A.; Crowe, Jack Claude; Cunning, John; Cupani, Lawrence; Curtiss, Marion; Custer, Bernardine
    - Calapai, Letterio, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Campanella, Vincent R., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Caseau, Charles, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Cavallon, Giorgio, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Chapman, Paul, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Cogan, Martin, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Cook, Gladys, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Cooper, Hilda, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Cornelius, Charles O., circa 1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Cosgrave John O'Hara, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Crimi, Alfred, 1936-1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - D, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Forms for the following artists: Dal Pino, Anthony; Dana, John; Daniels, Jacob Paul; Danshuk, George; Danziger, Isador; Darling, Mollie; Davenport, Millia; Davidson, Miriam; Davis, Charles W.; Davis, Wyatt; Day, Selma; Daz, H. (Day, Horace?); Deane, Margaret; de Aragon, Tiny; de Brennecke, Nina; de Cordoba, Mercedes (Mathilde); Decoursey (De Coursey), Nell; de Felipe, Juan; Delaney, Joseph; de Lasser, Yolande; Delman, Ben; Denner, Paul; de Rocco, Jovan; de Santis, Marcelloe; de Strange, Isabelle; de Vault, David S.; de Vegh, Geza; Devine, Daniel; de Wolfe, Henry; Dey, Maurice; Dezon, Sylvia; Diener, Irving; Dieterich, John; Dirk, Nathaniel; Doherty, James; Doktor, Raphael; Donaldson, Alice; Donnelly, John; Donovetsky, Ivan; Doran, Walter; Dorfman, David; Douglas, Laura Glenn; Dowling, William; Downer, Kenneth; Dreher, George; Driggs, Elsie G.; Drozdoff, Leo; Duany, Hester; du Bois, Guy Pene; Duci, Fortunato; Dukler, Samuel; Dunham, Francis; Dunne, Liam; Durant, Helen; Durin, Dorothy; Dyer, A.; Dyer, Briggs
    - Davis, Hubert, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Dean, Bob (Robert), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - de Kooning, Willem, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - de Marco, Jean, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - de Martini, Joseph, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Diller, Burgoyne Andrew, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Doi, Isami, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Drewes, Werner, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Dwight, Mabel, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - E, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Forms for the following artists: Earl, F.; Eberhardt, Patrick; Edwards, Paul; Egelson, James; Egri, R.; Eisman, Harry; Eldred, Thomas; Ellender, Raphael; Elliot, R.; Emanuel, Akiba; Emanuel, Herzl; Ennis, George Pearce; Ensel (Ensell), Henry; Essner, Evelyn
    - Englander, Florence A., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Epstein, Esther, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Epstein, Molly, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Ettinger, Stephen, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - F, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Forms for the following artists: Faber, Arthur; Fabry, Alois V. Jr.; Fastofsky, Joseph; Fatti, Alfeo; Fausett, W. Dean; Faye, Harold; Feinstein, David; Fenga, Michael; Ferrar, Louis M.; Ficini, Gino; Fidaroff (Fidoroff), Simon; Fields, Michael; Finestone, Bernard; Finley, Clemens; Fischer, Ulrich; Fischl, Alexander; Fishbein, Florence; Fitzgerald, Mary; Fletcher, D.; Floegel, Alfred; Flogsted, Louis; Fogg, Adalaide; Foley, Anna T; Foley, William; Fontanella, Henry F.; Ford, Mildred; Forgostein, Harold; Forman, Bessie; Forrester, Inglebord Emma; Forster, Mabel; Fowler, Catherine; Fox, Eva C.; Fox, Matthew; Foy, Hans; Frank, Bena V.; Frank, Herman; Frankel, Josephine Levy; Frankes, P.; Freed, Edward M.; French, Jared; Friedland, Jack; Friedman, Arnold; Friedman, Marc; Friedman, Samuel H.; Frisch, Sari; Froelich, Walter; Frutkoff, Louis S.; Fugarino, Paul; Fulda, Elizabeth; Fumagalli, Frank
    - Farnan, William, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Fastovsky, Isaac, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Feinsmith, Bernard, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Filmus, Tully, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Fleri, Joseph C., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Fogel, Seymour, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Fortess, Karl E., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Fox, Milton, 1968-1968 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Frankel, Max, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Freeman, Don, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - G-Gl, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      Forms for the following artists: Gaige, Richard; Galos, Ben; Ganso, Emil; Garfinkel, Sara; Leonard, Garfinkle; Garret, Adams; Gausser, E.; Gee, Yun; Gelb, Donald; Gelfand, Sydney; Gelman, Aaron; Genovese, Emanuel; Gerchik, Paul; Gernon, Dorothy; Gerstenfeld, Leonard; Gibbes, Winifred; Gibbo, Pearl; Gilbert, Wilson-Dorothy; Gilman, Aaron; Gilsleider, Edna J.; Giordano, Antonio (Antonia?); Girolami, George; Glassgold, Adolph; Glassgold, Harry; Glenn, Joseph; Glicenstein, Enrico; Glover, Joseph
    - Gm-Gz, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Forms for the following artists: Godfrey, Robert W.; Godsoe, Robert U.; Godwin, Earl; Goeller, Charles; Goldat, Isaac; Goldberg, Isidore; Goldfein, Abraham; Good, Minetta; Goodman, Job; Goodrich, Gertrude; Gordon, Benjamin; Gordon, Jean; Goreleigh, Rex; Gorelick, Boris; Gorid, Nicholas; Gottesman, Beatrice; Gottlieb, Abraham; Graham, F. Wynn; Grambs, Blanch; Granet, Henry; Graves, Morris C.; Gray, Marian; Green, Arthur; Green, Russell; Greenberg, Janet; Greenberg, Morris A.; Greene, Simon; Greenwald, Samuel; Gregory, Peter E.; Griffith, Herbert T.; Groth, John; Grubstein, Milton; Gussow, Bernard; Guteman, Ernest; Guyer, Irving
    - Geety, Weston Morley, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Geist, Sidney, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Gellert, Hugo, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Gerbino, Rosario, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Getz, Arthur, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Gikow, Ruth, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Gilbert, Blanche, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Gilien, Theodore, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Glickman, Maurice, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Goertz, August F., 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Gorky, Arshile, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Gottlieb, Harry, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Gould, Allan, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Graham, John, circa 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Greene, Balcomb, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Greene, Minna (Mina), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Greenwald, Sol, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Grossman, Elia, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Grunbaum, James, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Gugliemi (Guglielmi), Louis, 1937-1967 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Guston, Phillip, 1937-1940 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - H-He, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      Forms for the following artists: Hager, Lee; Hagopian, Charles; Hague, Raoul; Hain, Rosalyn; Halfant, Jules; Halls, Richard M.; Hamilton, Fred; Hammer, Amelia; Hannah, Rile; Hansen, Esther; Hantman, Murray; Hartman, Bertram; Hartman, Rosella; Hasenfratz, Lillian; Hauser, Alonzo; Hayes, Anastasie; Heald, Edna; Heckman, Albert; Heins, John P.; Heinz, Charles L.; Heliker, John E.; Heller, Helen West; Henning, Charles; Henoch, Hanley; Herlick, George; Herman, Andrew; Herrett, Emery
    - Hf-Hz, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      Forms for the following artists: Hicks, William; Hill, Carl; Himmel, Kaiman; Hirsch, Joseph; Hitesaw, Frank; Hobart, Helen; Hoffman, Melita; Holland, Robert D.; Holzhauer, Emil; Hondius, Gerritt; Hood, Hazel H.; Hopf, Ernest; Horn, Axel (Pinches); Horowitz, Frank; Howard, Mary; Howitz, Robert H.; Howland, Isabella; Hubbard, Athelina S.; Hubitschung, A.; Hunt, Courtney E.; Hunt, Thomas; Huntington, Robert; Hussar, Laci; Huston, Gene B.
    - Hannah, Muriel, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Hantman, Josephine Levy, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Harari, Hananiah, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Harriton, Abraham, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Harsanyi, Charles, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Hart, Agnes L., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Hartl, Leon, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Haucke, Friedrich, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Havens, Leonard M., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Hebald, Milton, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Hecht, Zoltan, 1936-1968 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Henkel, August H., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Henry, Charles Trumbo, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Hermes, Allen, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Hoffman, Seth, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Holmes, Henry, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Holty, Carl R., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Hutchison, Mary, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - I, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      Forms for the following artists: Irving, Ethel Helen; Irwin, Howard Lee; Ishigaki, Eitaro
    - Imlar, Edgar, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - J, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      Forms for the following artists: Jack, Mabel W.; Jacobs, Edward Deso; Jacobs, M. Lewis; Jacobs, Milton; Jacobson, Sidney; Jacoby, Carl; Jacoby (Jacobi), Samuel; Jakobson, Ruth; Janni, Pino; Jehu, Pauline; Jenkins, Leonard; Jerome, Mildred; Jewell, Emily; Joel, Robert (Spicer); Johnson, Arthur; Jonas, Robert; Jones, Alice; Julme, James S.; Juszko, Jeno
    - Jacobi, Eli, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Johnson, William H., circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Johnson, J. Theodore, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Jones, Wendell, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Joseph, Ronald, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Jules, Mervin, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Julius, Oscar H., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - K-Ke, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 105)
      Forms for the following artists: Kachinsky, Alexander; Kadowaki, Roy; Kadulin, Vladimir; Kallem, Henry; Kallman, I. Donskoy; Kaminsky, Dora; Kantor, Israel; Kantor, Joseph; Kantor, Morris; Karfunkle, David; Karlin, Agnes; Karlin, Gertrude (Karlan); Kasselau, Charles; Katz, David; Katz, Hilda; Katz, Hyman W.; Katz, Israel; Katzieff, Julius; Kaufman, Edward; Kaufman, Edwin; Kaufmann, Mortimer J.; Keene, Charles; Keller, Charles; Kempton, Martha; Kent, Florence; Kerkam, Earl (Erl); Kerner, Benjamin; Kerrwood, Arthur J.; Kessel, Dmitri
    - Kf-Kz, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      Forms for the following artists: Kieran, Dorothy; King, Alexander; Klein, Ray; Kleinman, Gladys; Kliban, Lucy; Klitgaard, Georgina; Klitgaard, Kat; Knapp, Leon; Knauff, Carl; Knight, Harry; Knotts, Benjamin; Koerner, Daniel; Kooltis, S.; Kopman, Benjamin; Korneth, Karl; Korodi, F.; Kosakoff, David; Koss, William; Kotin, Albert; Kovesi, Dezso; Kovner, Samuel; Kraska, Stanley; Krause, Erik Hans; Krause, Romnuald (Kraus, Romuald); Kriesberg, Irving; Kronfeld, Morris; Kufeld, Yankel
    - Kadish, Reuben, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Kaz, Nathaniel, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Kelly, Albert S., circa 1968 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Kent, Rockwell, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Killam, Walt, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Klein, Frank A., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Klonis, Stewart, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Konrad, Adolph, circa 1968 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Kovner, Saul, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Kroc, William, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Kruse, Alexander, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Kuniyoshi, Yasho, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - L-Le, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 119)
      Forms for the following artists: Lacey, Dorothy; Lances, Leo; Lane, Harry; Lane, Rosalia; Laning, Edward; Lansford, Alonzo M.; Laredo, Victory; Larsen, Peter; Larzelere, Fanchon; Lauro, Joseph; Lawler, Paul; Lawrence, William; Lawson, Ernest; Lazzari, Pietro; Leaf, Reuben; Lebduska, Lawrence; Leboit, Joseph; Lebreitstein, Alice; Lechay, James; Lechay, Myron; Le Fevere, Jules Z.; Lemberg, Gertrude; Lenbach, Joseph; Lenhard, Josef; Lenhard, Walmsley; Lessing, Charles; Lever, Hayley; Levine, Morris J.; Levinson, Abraham F.; Levinson, Benjamin; Levow, Irving; Levy, Martha; Lewis, Golda (Oleniker, Sahny); Lewis, Monty
    - Lf-Lz, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 120)
      Forms for the following artists: Liberte, L. Jean; Lieberman, Jacob E.; Lieberman, William; Lifschitz, Rae; Liguori, Charles; Lindenthaler, Charles; Lindermayor, John; Lindsey, Richard; Linshinsky, Rubin; Lipscomb, Isabel; Liroff, Gladys; Litchfield, Nell; Lomedico, Thomas G.; Lomoff, Joseph; Lonergan, Nora; Longchamps, Gaston; Loughridge, George; Lowell, Nat; Lowengrund, Margaret; Lowry, Mina; Lowther, Phillips; Luban, Boris; Lubin, Joseph; Lubovsky, Maxim; Lubrano, Joseph; Lucker, Paul; Ludins, Ryah; Luisi, Nicholas; Lumbard, Howard N.; Lunnon, James; Lurie, Nan; Luttrell, M.
    - Lawrence, Jacob, Jr., 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Lawson, Irene, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Lee, Doris, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Lefcourt, Irwin, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Lehman, Harold, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Levi, Julian E., 1937-1967 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Lewison, Florence, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Lightfoot, Elba, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Linding, Herman, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Liss, Abe, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Livingston, Rolland (Crawford, R.), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Locke, Charles, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Lonsbury, Earl, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Lo Pinto, Ferdinand, 1938-1967 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Ludins, Eugene, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Ludwig, Helen, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Lush, Viola (Vivian), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - M-Mc, circa 1967 (Box 5, Folder 138)